http://www.fmlink.com/privacy/

Close Skip to contentFM TopicsBuilding TypeBuilding SystemsFurnishings & InteriorsMaintenance & OperationsPlanningSafety & HealthSoftware & TechnologySustainabilityOtherAll TopicsNewsLatest PostingsDevelopmentsSurveysProducts & ServicesRegulations & GovernmentAssociations & OrganizationsContract AwardsNewsletter ArchiveEventsArticlesLatest PostingsMagazinesHow ToSustainabilityAnalyst InsightsBenchmarkingWorkplace StrategiesWhite PapersCase StudiesContact All ProvidersResourcesSpecial OffersLinksEducation & TrainingOrganizationsDirectoriesFM DirectorySustainability DirectoryAds & PressAdvertise on FMLinkSend a Press ReleaseContact Us Search for:
Follow FMLinkFollow us on FacebookFollow us on TwitterFollow us on LinkedInSubscribe to our RSS Feed Sign up for e-news
The following is the privacy policy for the FMLink website. In this policy, we describe what personal information we collect on our site, how we use it, and your options regarding information we may collect about you. If you have questions about this policy, please feel free to contact us at:FMLink Group, LLC, P.O. Box 18415, Washington, DC 20036-8415 info@fmlink.com | 301.365.1600Updated May 21, 2018  Information Collected…From All VisitorsWhile you are browsing the FMLink.com website, anonymous information will be gathered in our computer system log files. We use this information to administer our site and learn, for example, which content is most popular and which areas may be having performance problems. We have no way to relate this information to any one individual.In addition, we use a cookie called www.fmlink.com to log your path through our site. This cookie does not store any personally identifiable information about you, other than your IP Address. Nonetheless, you may choose to reject or delete the www.fmlink.com cookie at any time. To learn how to do this on your system, read your browser Help file. If you chose to reject this cookie, your experience in navigating FMLink may not be as productive, as you may see notices on each page.  The cookies help FMLink understand your interests, making it more likely that we will serve up content that is most meaningful to you. There also are cookies from GoogleAds and Google syndication (used by Google AdSense and DoubleClick).From Those Who Sign Up for an FMLink Mailing ListIf you have requested that FMLink send you its newsletters or other mailings, we will send it to your email address. Opting-out from either type of mail may be initiated from within the mail itself, by logging into your account, or by emailing info@fmlink.com.At no time will FMLink share your personal information with anyone outside of FMLink, including what lists you have signed up for. If you click on a link from within an email we send, even if it is from an FMLink advertiser, your personal information will not be shared.From Those Who Click on Advertisements on FMLinkIf you click on an advertisement served by FMLink, we will track that someone has clicked on the advertisement, but do not share that information with anyone outside of FMLink. You share it anonymously with the advertiser (i.e., your data is lumped with that of others in the form of aggregate data; none of your personal data, including your IP and email address, are provided to the advertiser).Besides banners served by FMLink third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website. Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting Ad Settings.From Those Who Have a Listing in FMLink’s FM Directory or Sustainability DirectoryIf you have signed up your Company for a listing in one of FMLink’s Directories, your personal information is maintained by FMLink, so we may send you mailings related to your listing and enable you to send us updates. We post only information that you had provided to us and asked to have us post. We do not share any of your personal information with anyone outside of FMLink.From Those Who Participate in FMLink SurveysIf you complete one of our surveys, the data we collect will not be aggregated with the registration data previously provided to FMLink. If the survey has been sponsored by a company external to FMLink, only data fully completed on the survey will be submitted to the surveying partner (not your personal information), allowing you to remain anonymous, unless you voluntarily chose to provide personal information for that particular survey.Updating your Information on FMLinkShould you be on FMLink’s email or announcement list and you wish to update it or remove yourself from the list, either click on the appropriate link from the bottom of one of the mailings or go to the registration form and simply check the boxes you would like to receive—we automatically will update your preferences. Alternatively, you may email us at info@fmlink.com.If you have signed your company up for an FMLink Directory and wish to modify your listing or information about a new contact person for FMLink, email us at info@fmlink.com with the details.More Information about Your Data Maintained at FMLinkHow Long FMLink Retains DataFMLink retains your tracking data (IP Address) for 26 months (tracking data enables us to understand which pages you visited when you were on FMLink). Your data regarding your subscription preferences (e.g., newsletter, announcements, Company information for FMLink’s Directories) is maintained indefinitely.Legal Basis for Use of Your DataBesides your IP Address, which was discussed above, FMLink maintains no other personal data that can be associated with you, other than what you provided to FMLink when you signed up for one of our mailing lists or to register your company for one of our Directories.How FMLink Uses the Data We CollectWhen you sign up for one of our mailing lists, we use that information to ensure that you receive the mailings that you request. We also use this to let our advertisers know how many people are signed up for our lists, as well as where they are from. All such data are provided in aggregate and never in the form of individual data about any specific subscribers. At no time is personal data about subscribers shared with anyone outside of FMLink.FMLink also uses information from our visitors to compile data about how they are using FMLink. This may include which pages are visited, where visitors go after seeing a specific page, how long they spend on pages, what they click on, etc. All such data are provided in aggregate and never in the form of individual data about any specific subscribers. At no time is personal data about subscribers shared with anyone outside of FMLink.Your Right to Access and Modify Your DataAnyone who has provided personal data to FMLink may email info@fmlink.com to request the following (Allow 10-14 days for any changes to be made):Details on the personal information retained by FMLink, and how it is being used.Additional information on how to modify the personal information retained by FMLink.Remove the personal information retained by FMLink (from individual mailing lists or from all lists).Remove oneself permanently from any or all mailing lists, one may do so by emailing info@fmlink.com or by clicking on the appropriate link from the bottom of any such email.Data Maintained by Others Outside of FMLinkFMLink has third-party applications outside of the control of FMLink that track user data anonymously on FMLink during a visit. Such applications include but are not limited to social media buttons (e.g., Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, Google Plus), Google Analytics (visitor behavior, including identification of most visited pages on FMLink), WordPress and its third-party plug-ins (enable FMLink to serve up content), PopupAlly (to enable visitors to sign up for newsletters and other mailings, as well as to provide consent to FMLink to use cookies) and DoubleClick for Publishers (tracking of advertisements). In no case does FMLink share any data provided by its visitors (e.g., one’s name, email address or company) with other entities outside of FMLink.In some instances targeted advertising may be displayed on FMLink, including by Google AdSense. Such third-party advertisers may collect and use your IP Address, which is outside of our control. This targeting may be caused by cookies already in place on your device.Updates to this PolicyAs our Web site evolves over time or our data-handling policies change, we will update this privacy policy. Changes will be effective 10 days following the posting of the new policy on the Web site. If we make significant changes to our data-handling practices, we will attempt to notify our active customers in other reasonable ways that may include an administrative email or other notice. This privacy policy will be governed by the laws of the United States and the State of Maryland.
The latest FM news, in your inbox sign-upThis site tracks visits anonymously using cookies. Click "Agree and Close" to confirm this is acceptable to you, or find out more through our Privacy Statement. This site tracks visits anonymously using cookies. Close this dialog box to confirm this is acceptable to you, or find out more through our Privacy Statement.
